<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Text View</string>
    <string name="fName">Mahadi_Hassan</string>
    <string name="fullName">Mahadi Hassan</string>
    <string name="mitebot"> <b>bold</b> and <i>italic</i> and <del>delete</del> <br></br><br></br>

    Technology is a big contribution in our lives. There are many hardware devices
        which make our life journey easier, make it more easier when it can be remotely controlled from
        anywhere.<br></br><br></br>\n  /n
        Why I decided to build a desktop application which name is “Mit-E Bot Controller”. This
        is capable to transmit data and received data at a time from device / hardware module via
        LAN and internet connection. By help of this remote user can able to command device and
        the monitoring also. This software is so flexible, it can easily connect the module via IP
        address or database connection.<br></br><br></br>
        There has two kind of connection method, users must have to connect one among them. If
        the module or hardware device is connected to a LAN connection, users need an IP
        address, or if the module or device is connected to the Internet, users have to provide the
        information of database server. Users must select one of them for connection. Once
        connected to the device with the remote, users can easily send signals and also receive
        signals from the device. One of the great advantage of this software is platform
        independent. This software can run on any operating system example like Windows, Mac,
        Unix, Linux kernel.<br></br><br></br>
        Some of the key features of this application are that it is able to stream live video, can
        provide digital and PWM signal and at a time can read three different kind of sensor value
        from module. The main interface of the “Mit-E Bot Controller” consists of three parts. On
        the left side is the transmission part, on the right side is the credentials information part of
        the device and on the right side is the receiver part.
        The install process of this software is very simple, users do not need to install any third
        party. Because I\'ve combined all the necessary file into a single setup file. Hopefully, it will
        give a good experience.

    </string>

</resources>